[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the scientific name of the Common Raccoon?", "correct_answer": "Procyon lotor", "incorrect_answers": ["Procyon cancrivorus", "Procyon nelus", "Procyon insularis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the island shared by Haiti and the Dominican Republic?", "correct_answer": "Hispaniola", "incorrect_answers": ["Ile dHaiti", "Isla Dominica", "Carib Island"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What name does the mouse think belongs to Thomas OMalley in the film The Aristocats?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["OBrien", "OGrady", "OToole"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Bitter melon, or bitter gourd, has been traditionally used by Asians, Panamanians and Colombians in the prevention and treatment of this disease.", "correct_answer": "Malaria", "incorrect_answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Rabies", "Tetanus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Himalayan range, part of which is Mount Everest, stretches across five different countries in Asia. Which of the following countries is not among them?", "correct_answer": "Israel", "incorrect_answers": ["Bhutan", "Pakistan", "India"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these is not a true breed of chicken. Which one?", "correct_answer": "Red-tailed", "incorrect_answers": ["Hamburg", "Plymouth Rock", "Leghorn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I have crossed oceans of time to find you. (1992)", "correct_answer": "Dracula", "incorrect_answers": ["Moulin Rouge", "Notting Hill", "A Knights Tale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Up In Smoke, what type of vehicle do Cheech and Chong drive across the Mexican border into America?", "correct_answer": "A delivery truck", "incorrect_answers": ["A school bus", "A station wagon", "A motorcycle and sidecar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In A Nightmare On Elm Street, Nancy lives on Elm Street, located in this fictional city in Ohio.", "correct_answer": "Springwood", "incorrect_answers": ["Derry", "Ambervale", "Blackwood County"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After years of calculations and observations of the results, mathematicians have found which of these statements about the mathematical constant pi to be true?", "correct_answer": "The digits of pi are equally distributed.", "incorrect_answers": ["The digits of pi eventually reach a point where they repeat their pattern.", "The number of 3s is larger than any other digit in pi.", "The number of 5s is larger than any other digit in pi."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was first to prove that beside an irrational number, pi is also transcendental number (i.e. is not a root to any polynomial equation with rational coefficients)?", "correct_answer": "Ferdinand von Lindemann", "incorrect_answers": ["Archimedes", "Leonhard Euler", "Augustin Cauchy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what geographical region is the Aye-aye indigenous?", "correct_answer": "Madagascar", "incorrect_answers": ["New Zealand", "Tasmania", "Hawaii"]}]